## **DANIEL MORI**

Full stack Developer lucky.goldragon@gmail.com

• 1304 MacLaren St Ottawa •

## Summary

Full-stack web developer with over 8 years of experience analyzing, designing, developing, and integrating front-end & back-end-based applications. Possesses knowledge of web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, AngularJS, Vue.js, Next.js, Node.js, Ajax, and PHP. Logical and results-driven full stack developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused websites and applications. Judicious and creative when crafting effective websites, apps and platforms to propel competitive advantage and revenue growth. Technically proficient and analytical problem solver with calm and focused demeanor.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### CodeBlue

### Senior Full Stack Developer

2021 - 2022

- Supervised 30 developers that created RW's e-commerce platform that could scale up to 1M daily visitors.
- Directed RW's technical support and operations teams to successfully solve over 400 customer complaints, maximizing uptime and achieving 90% customer satisfaction.
- Designed and developed over 15 full-stack solutions that solved 70% of use cases from embedded devices, and web UI to backend and database.
- Guided and managed a 15-member development team to grow their technical skills via mentoring on operational improvements, coding practices, and technical issue resolutions; improved productivity by 49%.

### InstaCoin

### Senior Full Stack Developer

2020 - 2021

- Worked on NFT minting/staking platforms on Ethereum, Solana, and Polygon networks
- Built NFT marketplaces on both Ethereum and Solana networks- Improved performance by integrating the Moralis API, Graph protocol, and OuickNode APIs
- Worked on the backend development using Node.js, Express.js and Nest.js
- Used Python, FastAPI and SQLAlchemy also to build the backend APIs
- · Worked on the frontend development using React.js, Web3.js, Vue.js, Tailwindcss, SASS, MaterialUI, DaisyUI, Ant Design, and ChakraUI
- With the fast development of landing/minting pages and NFT contracts and deployment and hosting of the platforms ono the cloud, could bring the platforms into the booming NFT market in a short time and bring the good sales to distributors
- Implemented staking/breeding/airdrop with ERC20 tokens and SPL tokens as rewards

#### **CSIRO**

## Full stack Developer

2017 - 2019

- Wrote front-end code, back-end code, integrated 4+ with frameworks and APIs, and utilized multiple CLI tools and configuration GUI's.
- Led architecture, design, and development of 30+ new features.
- Presented and conveyed ideas and designs with 4+ technical teams and 12+ business partners.
- Developed 40+ applications following Agile product development methodologies.
- Oversaw the development and maintenance of new products, technical documentation and workflows.
- Designed, built and automated data flows to save 10+ hours of tedious work per week

### AMR

### Front End Developer

2016 - 2017

- Contributed to the in-house UI library to create reusable components that saved over 200 hours of development time per month
- Developed user-friendly UI/UX web applications using React/Redux/Redux/Saga/AMD/Material-UI, Angular, Vue/VueX/Vuetify/Element-UI/Vue-Bootstrap, D3.is, three.js, Bootstrap/jQuery
- Created a web app MVP for a store delivery management platform with 100+ business customers to create, manage, and monitor deliveries using React and Redux
- Added new features to a meditation app with 5,000+ monthly active users to enable the uploading of audio and video content using React and Redux
- Through A/B testing of different components and combinations improved customer conversion rate by 17%, representing \$500,000+ in incremental annual revenue

### WORK EXPERIENCE

TEK systems

Front End Developer 2014 - 2016

- Created new features, functionality and capabilities on the eCommerce sites using Java, Ajax, SAS, and JSON.
- Built stable and maintainable codebases using React. Implementing a mobile-first approach to existing websites.
- Recommended solutions for a streamlined, user-friendly interface with the design team.
- Performed bug fixes and code reviews. Technical debt reduced by 32% within first month.
- Designed and implemented HTML email templates and newsletters for marketing campaigns.
- Consulted with 508 Compliance professionals during development of new websites to ensure accessibility.
- Ensured proper documentation and reports in all stages of product life cycles.

### Education

The University of Arizona

Executive MBA, Engineering Management

North Carolina Wesleyan College

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Tucson, AZ

2010 - 2013

Rocky Mount, NC

2006 - 2009

### **SKILLS**

Backdend Development:

AWS · AWS API Gateway · AWS Lambda · Python · Java · Node.js · Java Spring · Express · Django · Flask · FastAPI · Stripe · Nest

Frontend Development:

 $ES5/ES6 \cdot TypeScript \cdot SCSS \cdot CSS3 \cdot TailwindCSS \cdot React \cdot Next \cdot Gatsby \cdot Vue3 \cdot Nuxt \cdot REST \cdot GraphQL \cdot OAuth2 \cdot JWT \cdot Figma \cdot Zeplin$ 

Blockchain Development:

Smart contract · DeFi · NFT · DEX · Staking · Solidity · web3.js · ethers.js · OpenZeppelin · Rust · Golang ·

 $ERC-20/ERC-721/ERC-1155 \cdot BEP-20/BEP-721/BEP-1155 \cdot Truffle \cdot Hardhat \cdot Metamask \cdot Binance \ Wallet \cdot solana \cdot Ethereum \cdot Polygon$ 

Database: PostgreSQL · MySQL · MongoDB · AWS RDS · AWS Data API · AWS DynamoDB · Google FireStore

# Languages